Do you realize
this is probably
the last time we're
all going to be here
in the coffee house
as six single people.
Why, what's happening
to the coffee house?
Oh... okay.
Yep, from now on
it's going to be
the four of you guys,
and me and the missus.
The little woman,
the wife,
the old ball and chain.
Ha, old?
The young, hot
ball and chain.
That's much better.
Oh, we got to go.
Where are you guys going?
We're going to pick up
the wedding dress,
then we're going
to have lunch with Mom.
Oh... Joey, you're
having lunch with my mom?
No, I just heard "lunch."
But, yeah, I can go, sure.
You know, actually,
I'm kind of glad
they're leaving
'cause I need to talk
to you about something.
What's up?
Well, this may be
a little awkward...
Listen, if you
want to borrow money,
it's kind of a bad time.
I'm buying dinner
for 128 people tomorrow night.
It's not that.
Um, now, what
I'm going to say to you
I'm not saying
as your friend, okay?
I'm saying it as
Monica's older brother.
But you're still my friend.
Not for the next few minutes.
During this time,
are you still my best man?
Nope.
Do I still call you Ross?
Okay...
You guys are getting
married tomorrow
and-and I couldn't be more
thrilled for both of you.
But as Monica's older brother
I have to tell you this:
If you ever hurt
my little sister...
if you ever cause her
any unhappiness of any kind,
I will hunt you down
and kick your ass.
( laughing )
What? I'm serious.
Hey, dude, stop it, okay?
I'm not kidding, here.
Hey, I hear what
you're saying, okay?
And thanks for the warning.
No problem.
So are we friends again?
Yeah.
Okay.
You won't believe what Monica's
older brother just said to me.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Whatcha doing, Mon?
I'm making a list
of all the things
that are most likely
to go wrong at the wedding.
That way I can be prepared.
What are they?
Well, so far I have:
my bridesmaids' dresses
won't get picked up,
my veil gets lost,
or I don't have
my "something blue."
Hey, those are all the things
that I'm responsible for.
I had to go with the odds, Rach.
Hey, you guys!
Remember that audition
I had awhile ago
and I didn't get the part?
The commercial?
No.
That play?
That other play?
No.
The movie?
Yes!
Ooh!
The one about the pilot
and his dog who flies planes.
No, no, but, man,
that one hurt. Yeah.
No, this is the one
about the soldiers
who fight in World War I.
Oh, yeah, mm-hmm.
Back then, you know,
we called it The Great War.
It really was.
Well, anyway,
the guy they wanted backed out
and now they want me.
I start shooting today!
Congratulations!
Wait, you can't
start today.
Today is the
rehearsal dinner.
Oh, no, I'll be done by then.
Oh, well, then, way to go,
you big movie star!
I know. All right, I'll see
you guys over there.
I'm off to fight the Nazis.
Oh, wait, Joey!
We fought the Nazis
in World War II
not World War I.
Whoa, okay.
Who was in World War I?
Go ahead.
You're going to be late,
go, go!
Yeah, see you!
Who did we fight
in World War I?
Mexico?
Yes, very good.
Of course.
Hey, Joey,
we're ready.
Yeah, me, too.
Richard, we're
ready for you.
Joey Tribbiani.
This is Richard Crosby.
He's playing Vincent.
I'm doing my scenes with you?
Nice to meet you, Joey.
Wow, I can't believe this.
This is incredible.
I mean, you just won an Oscar.
No, I didn't.
I think you did.
I think I lost, three times.
Uh, um, cookie, would you...
Okay, we're about
an hour away
from getting
the scene lit
so, uh, if you
guys don't mind
can we run it
a couple of times?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, all right,
let's do it.
( clearing throat )
And... action!
We have to find
the rest of the platoon.
Forget the platoon,
the platoon is gone!
What?
The platoon is dead.
Face facts, Tony.
So what are we going to do?
We have no reinforcements,
no food.
No, we still have
food in the basement.
I saw potatoes
and some dry pasta.
Hang on a minute.
Joey, you keep
touching your face.
Is something wrong?
No, no...
I, uh, I thought it might be
kind of a cool
character thing, you know?
He's a-- he's a face-toucher.
( no audio )
I don't think so.
Let's take it back
to Richard's last line.
Action!
We may not have any weapons
but we still have
food in the basement.
I saw potatoes
and some dry pasta
and a few tins of tuna.
Honey, we got to go!
Okay, here's a question
you never want
to have to ask.
My dad just called
and wanted to know
if he could borrow one
of your pearl necklaces.
Did he say what kind
of neckline he'd be wearing?
No.
Well, I've only met him once
but I'm guessing "plunging."
Yeah, he is more of
a "if you got it, flaunt it"
kind of... father.
I don't have
anything like that
but let me go see
if Rachel does.
Yes, include
more people in this.
Hey, do you realize
that at this time tomorrow
we're going
to be getting married?
Wait a minute,
I have a date tomorrow night.
I just, I can't
believe that we made it.
Well, you don't have to sound
so surprised.
I'm sorry, but...
Nothing.
What?
Well, honestly
ever since we got engaged,
I've been waiting
for something to flip you out.
Honestly... me, too.
Really?
Yeah, you know,
I keep thinking
that something stupid
is going to come up
and I'll go all...
well, Chandler.
But nothing has.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Thank you so much for
staying so calm during this.
I mean, it's really,
it's made me stay calm.
I could have been worse.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
( phone ringing )
MONICA:
Hi, if you're calling
before Saturday
you've reached
Monica and Chandler.
But if you're calling
after Saturday
you've reached
Mr. and Mrs. Bing!
Please leave a message
for the Bings!
Hey, Maureen, hi!
Gosh, Chandler,
this is my cousin Maureen.
We're the Bings.
Hi, oh, you guys
look so beautiful.
Mr. and Mrs. Bing.
Wow, Monica...
Hey, just so you know
I had my "older brother
talk" with Chandler.
What is that?
Well, I told him that
if he ever hurt you
I would hunt him down
and kick his ass.
( laughter )
What, what is the matter
with everybody?
I'm serious,
I would kick his ass.
( screaming laughter )
Oh, Ross,
please, my makeup!
Hi...
Chandler!
...Mom.
Thanks for wearing...
something.
Oh, honey, this
is so exciting.
I thought we'd screwed
you up so bad
this day would never come.
And just think--
soon there'll be
lots of little Bings.
I can't believe I have to go
back to work after this
and get spit on again.
Well, you're lucky.
At least the people
that spit on you are famous.
Who spits on you?
I don't want to
talk about work.
Mrs. Bing,
these are my parents
Judy and Jack Geller.
It's lovely to meet you.
So, are you his mother
or his father?
Jack!
What, I've never
seen one before.
Dad, there's Ross.
Why don't you go talk to him?
I didn't even have a chance to
act as though I'm okay with it.
Hello, all.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, Mr. Bing.
Nora.
Charles.
It's so great
to see you both here.
Yes.
Although I think
we may be seeing
a little too much
of some people.
Aren't you a little old
to be wearing a dress like that?
Don't you have
a little too much penis
to be wearing
a dress like that?
Oh, my God.
Of course you can
kick his ass, son.
You could kick anyone's ass
you want to.
Thanks, you guys.
Oh, Rach, Rach...
Hey, could you
do me a favor
and would you talk
to Chandler's dad
and try to keep him
away from Chandler's mom?
Yeah, but I don't know
what he looks like.
He is the man
in the black dress.
Man in the black...
Oh...
Hi, I'm Rachel.
I'm a friend of
Monica and Chandler's.
I'm Amanda.
Oh, I get it.
A-man-duh!
( laughing )
( clinking glass )
Could I have everyone's
attention, please?
Uh, I'm, uh, I'm Ross Geller.
Dr. Ross Geller!
Dad, please.
As I was saying,
I'm Dr. Ross Geller
uh, and I'm the best man
and this marriage
is doubly special for me
because not only
is the groom my best friend
but the bride
is my little sister...
and she's the greatest sister
a guy could ask for.
So if you'd all please join me
in raising a glass
to the couple we're
here to celebrate...
To the Bings.
ALL:
To the Bings!
I'm going to go
steam my wedding dress, okay?
Who wants the responsibility
of making sure
nothing happens to it?
I'll do it.
Who wants it? Anybody?
I said I'll do it.
Nobody wants to do it?
All right, I'll do it myself.
Monica, I'm not
going to screw it up.
You know what?
You're right, I'm sorry.
Actually,
you were a big help tonight.
Yeah, and thanks for putting
my grandmother in the cab
and making sure
she got to the hotel safely.
Well, of course,
that is what I'm here for.
Okay, sorry.
Oh...
What grandmother?
Hey, where have you been?
Taking my parents
back to the hotel.
Are you going
back to work?
Yeah.
Nice shades.
Thanks, I figure if
I wear these in my scenes
at least I won't get spit
in my eyes, you know?
And, if I remember correctly
Ray-Ban was the official
sponsor of World War I.
Great!
All right.
I'll see you later.
Hey, where's Chandler?
I think he's in Rachel's room.
See you.
Chandler.
Chandler?
( knocking )
Hey, is, uh...
is Monica here?
She's steaming her dress.
Why, what's up?
I think Chandler's gone.
What?
He left that.
"Tell Monica I'm sorry."
Oh, my God.
What's up?
"Tell Monica I'm sorry."
Tell her yourself.
Oh, my God.
Chandler just
left though?
Yeah, but maybe
it's not what we think.
Maybe it's...
"Tell Monica I'm sorry...
I drank the last of the milk."
Or maybe he was writing
to tell her that...
that he's changed
his name, you know.
"Tell Monica I'm Sorry."
I think it means
he freaked out and left.
Don't be so negative.
Good God,
isn't it possible
that Sorry is sitting
in there right now?
Okay, Phoebe...
I think Ross is right.
What are we
going to do?
Look, okay, I'm just
going to...
I'm going to have
to go find him
and bring him back, okay?
You make sure Monica
does not find out, okay?
Okay, but if you don't
find him and bring him back
I am going to hunt you down
and kick your ass.
I will... I will find him.
Joey, can you go through
these lines with me?
Oh, man, they just
redid my makeup.
Just the last
two pages.
All right.
I found the picture.
The picture?
What picture?
The picture of my wife
I found in your pack.
Could you, uh... could
you lower the script?
I don't want to.
I need to see your face
so I can play off your reaction.
Okay, look, um...
I know you're
this great actor
and you play all those
Shakespeare guys and stuff
but you're spitting
all over me, man.
Well, of course I am.
You know you've
been spitting on me?
That's what real
actors do.
Enunciation is the mark
of a good actor.
And when you
enunciate... you spit.
Wow. Didn't know that.
Thanks.
Okay, okay, check it out.
Picture? What picture?
( spits )
Huh?
Gunther, have you, uh,
have you seen Chandler?
No, no, I haven't seen him.
Oh, damn.
He's getting married
tomorrow, right?
Yes, yes. Don't worry,
everything's fine.
We'll see you tomorrow
at the wedding.
I wasn't invited.
Well, then, we'll see you
the day after tomorrow.
Mom? Dad?
Wha-what are you guys
doing here?
Well, you kids talk
about this place so much
we thought we'd see what
the fuss is all about.
I certainly see why
the girls like coming here.
Why?
The sexy blonde
behind the counter.
Gunther?
Your mother just added
him to her list.
What? Your list?
Yeah, the list of people
we're allowed to sleep...
No, no, I know,
I know what the list is.
Come on, sit down,
have a cup of joe.
Dad, I can't. I'm sorry.
Look, if you see Chandler
could you just let him know
that I'm looking for him?
And if you see Rita Moreno
let her know
I'm looking for her.
MAN:
Action.
I found the picture.
What picture?
The picture of my wife
in your pack.
You went through
my personal property?
Why do you have a picture
of Paulette in your pack?
Because, Vincent,
we were lovers...
for two years.
Cut. Wonderful.
Great scene, huh?
You were awesome, man.
And that last speech,
you soaked me.
Thanks a lot.
Here's your call sheet
for tomorrow.
Oh, I'm not
working tomorrow.
You are now.
Oh, no, I can't.
You got to get me out of it.
I have plans,
important plans.
Ross said there's still
no word from Chandler.
Oh, man.
Oh, but he did say
that they found
the grandmother wandering
down Fifth Avenue.
Okay, well, there's one down.
I'm getting married today...!
Think I just cracked a rib.
But I don't care
because today's my wedding day!
My day is finally here!
You know, she might not
even notice he's gone.
I'm going to start
getting ready!
We can't let her start
getting ready.
This is too awful.
Shh.
Oh, God, but wait,
she'll be in the gown,
and then he won't show up,
and then she's going to have
to take off the gown,
and it's just...
Stop it, stop it, Rachel.
You can't do this here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's just...
it's just so sad.
You've got to pull
yourself together.
Monica can't see you
like this.
Then she'll know
something's wrong.
I know, I know.
There's no tissue.
Can you grab me
some toilet paper?
Oh, that's gone, too.
This is Monica's
bathroom, right?
Oh, I found one.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, God.
Can I have another one?
Sure.
Do you need some floss?
Oh, God, I just
cannot imagine
what is going to happen
if Chandler doesn't show up.
Oh, here's a whole bunch.
I mean, she's going
to be at the wedding
waiting for him
and people will be whispering,
"Oh, that poor girl."
You know, and then she'll have
to come back here
and live all alone.
Oh, my God.
What?
There was a pregnancy test
in the garbage
and it's positive.
Monica's pregnant.
So I guess she won't
be totally alone.
Next time on Friends...
We've got to tell
her that he's gone.
No! Hey, hey, we can't!
She's going to start
getting ready soon.
Can't you at least
stall her a little?
I'm never gonna
get married!
We've just got
one short scene
it's just you
and Richard
and, God knows,
he's a pro.
Are you drunk?
No!
Yes, you are.
All right.
Hey, how's Chandler doing?
Great.
Where are you?
I'm still on the set.
This is turning into
the worst wedding day ever.